http://www.jeffgordonfoundation.org/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
Terms and conditions
Jeff Gordon Children’s Foundation privacy policy
Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement (this “Statement”) discloses the privacy practices for JeffGordonFoundation.org (the “Website”) – what information we gather, how we use it and how to correct or change it. This Statement only addresses our activities from our servers. Other sites (including those to which the Website links and third party sites or services with which JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org) may have their own privacy policies and practices, which we do not control.
General privacy information
JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org contains links to partners, advertisers and third party Internet sites and services who may collect data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, e-commerce, etc. They each have separate privacy and data collection practices; independent of JeffGordonFoundation.org and JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information on any online service or website — for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas — that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Further, while we strive to protect your personal information, JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.
Use of information
All of the information JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org collects, both what you tell us and what we collect through the use of cookies, is “aggregated” — meaning that the information from many users is grouped together in a way that does not disclose the personal information of any particular user. We may use this aggregated information to evaluate which products and services are successful and which ones are not, and in order to evaluate which new services we should make available on JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org. We may use only the anonymous click stream data to help our advertisers deliver better-targeted advertisements. JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org will not disclose any information about any individual without the individual’s consent, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process. There may be cases in which some of your personal information may be used by jeffgordonchildrensfoundation.org to target e-commerce promotions and telemarketing activities. In addition, it may be shared with Third parties who assist JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org in producing its websites or provide a service to JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org users.
Contacting the website
If you have any questions about this Statement, the practices of jeffgordonchildrensfoundation.org with respect to personal information or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at info@jgcf.org.
Children under the age of 13
We do not currently collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. Under certain circumstances, visitors may be asked to submit a screen name as a means of identifying communications to JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org. Children of any age should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. If in the future, JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org collects personally identifiable information from children, it will do so in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (is U.S.C. 6501 et seq.).
Cookies
A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you’ve visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. This random number lets us keep track of “how many” times customers are doing specific things – like visiting our site each month – without really knowing who those customers are. We also use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your member ID. Additionally, after you’ve entered your member ID and password during a session on our service, we save that information so you don’t have to reenter it repeatedly during that session. Users should be aware that JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies maybe necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org.
Contests
We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for their contact information. The customer’s contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary for winner notification and prize delivery confirmation. The majority of the contests that we offer are hosted on the JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org; however, there may be cases in which a third party sponsor will host the contest and collect user information. In those cases, we urge users to review the privacy statement of the third party site. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings.
Security
JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org utilizes a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. All user contact information is contained behind a “firewall” and only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to production systems. Passwords and credit card numbers are encrypted in JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org’s secure database, which is also located behind a firewall. All sensitive/credit information supplied by users is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted in JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org’s databases as stated above. Because credit card information has been encrypted, it is completely invisible to any employee who accesses it, including our customer service team. If you desire to change your password, the customer service representative will reset to a new one after you have properly identified yourself. JeffGordonChildrensFoundation.org’s technology department conducts frequent site security audits and employs a third party audit company to perform additional site security audits.
